I am a replacement for my older
sister, Anastasia, who passed away.
I came here for the purpose
of a political marriage...
as no more than a mock fiancée, and yet...
Please tell me about yourself.
Things... I like.
Marie
is
Life
Oh, Marie...
Master.
Episode 4 "I've Found the Things I Like"
Mio, if you're here, please say something!
I just did.
Seeing Marie after four days
apart, what did you think?
I love her!
Not what I meant.
She's grown even more beautiful!
Five days ago,
you said to provide Lady Marie with our utmost
hospitality, and everything she truly deserves.
You did say that, correct?
Yes.
Her treatment in the baron's
household was clearly wretched.
Marie believes herself to be
ugly and unworthy of love.
So I want to give her every luxury she
desires so that she can build some confidence.
I want her to know that
she is worthy of that.
No matter how many luxuries
you may pile before her,
Lady Marie will likely avoid them.
What?
Master.
I am an abandoned child, but I was lucky
enough to be taken in by Lady Liu Liu.
I was elevated to the position of
head chamberlain of Granado Castle,
a position far above my
station, by you, master.
For that, I owe you an
immense debt of gratitude.
What is all of this? It isn't like you.
It is because of this that I can
understand a little of Lady Marie's feelings.
What it's like to go from a life of oppression
to becoming a resident in a gleaming castle...
and the fear that creates.
The sudden appearance
of a charming prince...
all the dresses and
shoes, bestowed upon her...
She wonders if it's all some ephemeral
magic, that will one day suddenly disappear.
It won't disappear.
Marie is beautiful and intelligent.
Mio, you're a brilliant head chamberlain,
and Liu Liu thinks of you
as her own daughter.
That isn't magic, it's reality.
Yes, you're right.
Master, you are exactly as you should be.
Please continue believing in the truth
of these commonplace things.
Are you being sarcastic?
Not at all. I'm complimenting you
from the bottom of my heart.
Tomorrow, I'll have to leave
the castle on business again.
I want you to use your discretion to
ensure that Marie is comfortable here.
May I also review issues
pertaining to personnel?
You may.
Those are the words I've waited for.
Still...
Is it all right for Marie
to be that adorable?
What?
She's so elegant dressed up,
but splendid in lounge wear, too.
Will this take long?
Smart and well-read, yet so naïve.
She stirs my protective instincts!
She's a good listener and fun to talk to.
She's brimming with a sparkling curiosity!
Her smiling face and laugh have
the impact of a ballista strike!
Her figure makes everything look stunning.
You're speaking incredibly quickly.
We're talking about those
looks with that personality!
The synergy increases her
adorableness a hundredfold!
Master, I don't think you're in
a position to speak of others.
Huh?
Please go to sleep now.
If you don't, you'll regret it tomorrow.
Marie is Life
I can't sleep.
Now, then. I've received permission
to redirect personnel.
I should take action as soon as possible.
Is this an appropriate quantity?
Yes! I will be able to finish all of this.
That was delicious!
Please allow me to join you.
What? You don't mind?
While you are dining, I have
my work as your server,
but I can accompany you for tea.
I'm so happy!
Mio, I've been wanting to have
tea with you for so long!
Oh!
Mio, if you're here, does that mean
that Lord Kyros has already left?
No, we've switched assignments.
Ilza and Hannah are serving the master.
I thought that might be best for everyone.
I see...
She's right. I'm certain they'll be happier
if they're able to serve real nobility.
Come in!
My lady! I, Toppo, have brought
my latest delicious experiment!
Would you like some?
I would!
A white... pudding?
It's a blancmange made with
almond flour and fresh milk!
Miss Mio, you should have some, too.
Oh, it's so jiggly!
Delicious!
Toppo's food really is
the best in the world!
I must hurry and make enough
for everyone in the castle!
I, Toppo, will take my leave now!
Wait!
It's just that Ilza and Hannah
may not like milk very much.
I haven't heard anything about that.
But when I asked for milk for my tea,
they said that was a novel way to drink it.
What?
It must be that they don't like milk.
Would it be possible to make
those without using milk?
Understood, my lady! I will give it a try!
Thank you, Toppo!
Lady Marie, you are...
I'm sure that Ilza and Hannah will
be shocked at how delicious it is.
Oh! My lady!
I was just on my way to your room.
Tomas, what is that?
It arrived for my lady.
It's from her family, the
house of Baron Shaderan.
Tomas! Why did you bring that here?!
B-But the master said that anything
from the House of Shaderan
should be given to the lady if
her attendants said it was okay.
If you know that, then why?
I haven't inspected that!
What? But Miss Hannah and Miss Ilza looked
it over and said to take it to the lady.
These are, without a doubt, my things.
Congratulations on your engagement.
You left behind some essential items
for your work in the count's household.
"The Story of the Raggedy Red Cat."
The thread in the binding has
been frail for a while,
but I'm certain that I
put it away carefully.
I-I'm sorry! I've done
something awful, haven't I?
What are you doing? Hey, let me go!
Release me immediately!
Hey!
That hurt.
How dare you?! You're just a maid!
And so are the two of you.
What?! We served the third prince
in the palace, you know?
Prince Luiphon recommended us
to Granado Castle personally!
And I am the head of the servants
here at Granado Castle.
You're just some old-timer.
You were just demoted to serving
the daughter of a destitute baron.
And I was the one who
arranged for that transfer.
Don't talk down to me.
Actually, it's well known, isn't it?
The countess is a barbarian,
and a former prostitute, who set up her
child with a client as a maid here.
What? I thought the child was an orphan,
abandoned on the side of the road at birth.
She lacks a surname.
It's hilarious to think she's
serving in a count's castle!
I see. So you truly are imbeciles.
What did you just say?
Now, it's your turn.
No!
My deepest apologies. This is all due
to my ineptitude as a supervisor.
It's all right. More importantly,
may I borrow some scissors and thread?
Johan!
My lady!
Y-Your clothes...
I remade some of my old clothes.
You said you'd show me around
the garden, didn't you?
Getting these a bit dirty is fine.
Is that all?
There were plenty of servants' shoes
I could have offered you.
Oh! Yes, we could have done that!
Well, no matter.
I've realized it for the first time.
The things I like...
I always thought I was doing
everything for my family,
but the truth is all the
hard labor felt like nothing...
because of how much I love
growing delicious vegetables.
I really do have things I like
and things I want to do.
I'm sorry I was brusque
toward you before now.
I thought that I shouldn't cause trouble for
you, the count's lady, by speaking to you.
Trouble?
I am a servant. And I'm a foreigner.
That doesn't matter.
We're living in the same house.
That makes us family, doesn't it?
I-I haven't officially become his fiancée
yet, but everyone here seems like a family.
You say the same things as the master does.
As Lord Kyros?
My lady!
The master is leaving!
Lord Kyros!
Oh, Marie.
The master stayed up all
night, so he's rather exhausted.
Last Night
Oh, Marie! I love you, Marie!
My, he truly is busy, isn't he?
More importantly, master, if you will be
visiting the palace for an evening party...
Let us go!
Stay away, you filthy servant!
You're filthy and you stink!
please return that dead
weight to Prince Luiphon.
D-Did you just call us dead weight?
We're here at his recommendation!
That's right! He said that one
day, we'd be his concubines.
All of this...
...is your fault!
You're just the daughter of a
broke baron lured by money!
You're no more than your
dead sister's replacement!
Everyone knows Shaderan's youngest
daughter is a losing prospect.
And it's the count who will be a
laughingstock for pulling the short straw!
Lord Kyros... a laughingstock?
You need to learn your place!
Ugly wench!
What part of her?
Try saying that again.
What part of my family,
of Marie, do you find ugly?
No, it's just...
And all this talk of noble
houses and money...
those aren't things that
belong to you, are they?
Are either of you more beautiful than
Marie? More honorable? More clever?
Cuter? Are you any of those things?
What about you could I possibly love?
Please, tell me.
Because I can't find a single thing.
Take them away.
Yes, sir!
I'm so sorry.
For what?
They said I'm the reason
they'll laugh at you, Lord Kyros.
Marie.
You are beautiful.
There's nothing here to laugh at.
Your beautiful red hair,
set off so well by this green...
Your eyes that shine like stars...
Your overflowing knowledge and curiosity...
Your innocent smile when you
speak of things you love...
Altogether beautiful.
Ahem.
Master, we are out of time.
We can wait another few seconds,
but I'm certain that wouldn't suffice.
What? Y-Yes.
Oh, the poor master.
And just when he was so close.
I only came for herbs to
use in some treatments,
but I managed to witness
something very nice.
Don't you agree?
Do you think the oregano
I grew was useful?
They saw
everything...
I was told that Lord Kyros was going
to the royal palace for a ceremony,
and that he would be away for ten days.
When he returned,
Marie! I will return soon!
we would begin arrangements
for our betrothal ceremony in earnest.
There's nothing here to laugh at.
That's what Lord Kyros said, but...
This is...
It isn't meant to be a threat, is it?
No, it isn't. It's written as an invitation.
"Lady Marie Shaderan,"
"I wish to congratulate you upon your
betrothal to my old friend Count Kyros Granado."
It's normal up to that point.
"As such, we have planned a special
event utilizing our means and efforts."
"Notice has been spread throughout the royal
capital, and the people eagerly await the day."
"Lady Marie, should you be unable to attend,
everything will have been for naught."
"The people will despair, and their
distress shall surely span generations."
"Please, you simply must attend."
It certainly does sound like a threat.
This gentleman is a prince, isn't he?
Yes.
He is the third prince and the
captain of the Royal Knights.
He has quite an open-hearted personality.
The fact that this arrived
on the eve of the event
shows that he expects you to attend.
Wh-What is this?
A chariot from the Royal Knights.
A-And this is...
A military fortress for the Kingdom of Diltz,
the stronghold of the Royal Knights.
A-Am I going to be publicly executed?
Please calm down.
B-But why the fortress?
I could have been with
Lord Kyros if it were the palace.
Prince Luiphon is the one who
recommended Hannah and Ilza.
He must want to apologize.
Returned Goods
That only increases my fear of an execution.
Is something wrong?
If Prince Luiphon is the host, he likely
has some amusing plans in place.
Plans?
Monster scares...
A rain of onions from above...
Or perhaps a pool full of jelly...
Just what sort of person is Prince Luiphon?
Well, he is not a villain.
Since we're here, I believe
we should enjoy the fun.
It's all so lively.
It's been fifty years since the
war. The world is at peace.
This sort of excitement
is good entertainment.
Please have one.
Th-Thank you.
When did she buy this?
First, I should go and greet
Prince Luiphon, right?
No, he probably isn't waiting
for a greeting from you.
It's possible that he hasn't
even come here at all.
What? So, I'm meant to simply
enjoy the festivities and leave?
Who can say? I don't understand what goes
on in Prince Luiphon's head at all.
I feel like Mio is a little
harsh towards the prince.
I wonder, does this feel like a small
event for someone of the royal family?
No, events on this scale are fairly rare.
What concerns me...
is that not a single rumor of it
reached us at Granado Castle.
If Prince Luiphon issued a gag order before
executing these arrangements, then...
I have a bad feeling about this.
M-Mio?
Prince Luiphon!
Where? What does he look like?
Down on the left by the stone wall.
Silver hair, wearing a
knight's military uniform.
Mio, how can you see so well?
I will go and check. Lady Marie,
please wait for me here.
I-I'll go with you!
It may be that he's made one of his
men dress as him to lure us out...
as part of a plan to suddenly
appear and scare you, Lady Marie.
What?
Don't move from this spot until I return.
No matter who calls out to
you, please ignore them.
I-I will!
I will return shortly!
No matter what happens,
I won't take a single step!
Hello? Standing right in front of my
shop like that is a problem for me!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Looking for contestants
for an apple peeling contest!
Contestants for an apple peeling contest?
That sounds like fun!
Excuse me, I'd like to try!
What? That's unusual.
I thought that noble
girls didn't use knives.
I-If a noble's wife peeled apples...
would it make her husband
a laughingstock, too?
What are you talking about?
You've gotta peel an apple to eat it, right?
And our apples are delicious!
A Certain Prince Affiliated
with the Knights
They've got the knights'
seal of approval, you know?
Yes, they look quite delicious!
I'd very much like to compete.
All righty then!
If you can peel an entire apple
within the time limit,
I'll give you an entire box of apples!
Start on my mark.
Yes, sir.
Then, here we go!
What a delicious-looking apple.
Th-That's mine! Please give it back!
Hmm, what to do?
Hey!
Come on! Over here!
Maybe you don't really want it after all?
Oh! My apple!
Yes, this is a good year for them, isn't it?
Honestly. My customer was
enjoying herself, you know?
Here's the
money
What point is there in the host
ruining it all, Your Highness?
What? "Your Highness"?
Now, now. I simply wanted to have a
little fun with my friend's fiancée.
Right?
S-So this gentleman really is...
THUD THUD THUD
So it was a trap after all,
wasn't it, Prince Luiphon!
I am Luiphon Sandhalkia Diltz,
third prince of this land and
captain of the knights.
But perhaps most of all...
I am dear Kyros' friend!
Pleased to meet you, sweet Marie!
S-So this is the sort of person he is.
Hey there, everyone!
I am Prince Luiphon!
Kyros and I have been the best of
friends since our school days!
Is sweet Marie worthy
of being his betrothed?
I will ascertain the truth of
it through a special surprise!
Next time, "The Prince and
the Pitch-Black Warrior."
Episode 5 "The Prince and the Pitch-Black Warrior"
You'll come and watch, of course, won't you?